what's the best way to deal with anxiety
caused by
trt trt does not cause anxiety unless
you're an anxious person to begin with
and you believe that TI is a reason to
be anxious remember depression is
dwelling on the past and anxiety is
dwelling on fear of the future and if
you fear something you're going to be
anxious there's no direct mechanism by
which properly administered key term
properly administered and managed trt
increases anxiety low testosterone can
lead to
anxiety uh because it actually reduces
confidence levels and when we don't feel
well our our our hope for the future our
Outlook is diminished and that increases
anxiety because remember I said anxiety
is fear of the future and if your future
looks Grim you're going to be anxious if
your future looks bright your anxiety is
reduced but if you're a type of person
who anticipates things expects things
that are unrealistic and then they don't
occur that leads to again hopelessness
for the future because you have failed
to meet expectations that El lead
anxiety so setting correct expectations
with a patient UPF front is a provider's
responsibility but the patient's
responsibility is to accept that and not
think that trt is going to fix every
problem in their life